One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The clouds floating in the cobalt blue,
got lost and will soak us all tomorrow.
It'll be fine if you just smile before the sunset.
If it's your wish, you can just
say a spell in your chest.
For your hopes...
Our quick premonition
is showing in the rainbow colored music notes.
Won't you come with me?
We're fallen angels,
we'll fire arrows into your dreams.
What color shall we add
into the cobalt blue?
Destroy the sad reality that reflects in your eyes.
Let's raise our wings, full of warmth.
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts.
The Circling Bounties and
The Duel on Banaro Island!
Speaking of the judiciary island Enies Lobby,
After causing a disturbance on the entranceway of the World Government,
Both the marines and pirates won't be able to remain silent.
Right now, the strawhat pirates' name is resounding in the whole world.
Along with this poster.
Sanji is the best!
East Blue
Floating Restaurant Baratie
Isn't it amazing, customers?!
It's just like the real thing!
This is the home of the 77 million belly bounty Black Leg Sanji!
Welcome to the Floating Restaurant Baratie!
Foosha Village Luffy's hometown
East Blue
Party!
Today we party!
For the most expensive guy in the east!
300 million bounty!
A toast for our Luffy!
Be silent!
Show some manners! Manners!
Cheers!
Hey!
Geez...
No one listens to what the mayor says.
Seems like he's having fun.
He's even got this cute pet.
These must be Luffy's friends.
You call these criminals friends?!
An enemy to the whole world came from our village!
I've never heard of a pirate declaring war on the World Government!
That's true...
What does that Garp think he's doing?!
Letting his own grandson cause such a terrible incident.
What's wrong with those three guys...
I wonder if Dadan knows about this...
Cheers!
I told you to be quiet!
East Blue
Syrup Village Usopp's hometown
Sogeking, the King of the Snipers...
You're right!
There's no doubt about it!
This is Usopp-san!
Right?!
This nose is the Captain's, right?!
The villagers don't believe us!
He's worth 30 million!
But we knew Kaya-san would recognize him!
Nobody knows the awesomeness of the Captain!
Captain is a man who turns all lies into truth!
This mask is so cool!
Let's make some clay replicas!
Where are you going Kaya-san?
I'm gonna continue my medical studies.
I have to become one fine doctor!
So even if Usopp-san comes back injured, I can cure all of his wounds!
I'm jealous of the Captain...
We'll kick his ass if he makes Kaya-san sad.
East Blue
Shimotsuki Village Zoro's Hometown
Sensei! Sensei!
Is it true that the Pirate Hunter Zoro once studied at this dojo?!
Yes, it's true.
But I forbid you to look up to him!
Why?! He's so cool!
Please show us how to be pirates too!
I didn't teach him how to become a pirate.
Really?!
Don't lie, sensei!
I also wanna become such an amazing swordsman!
My, my, what a terrible elder they have chosen.
I was surprised about the events on Judiciary Island, but...
Me too!
Zoro-kun, it seems you have no regrets.
No matter what kind of person you become,
It's fine a long as you treasure your way of the sword.
East Blue
Cocoyashi Village Nami's Hometown
Gen-san!
Here are the oranges.
What, you brought them again, Nojiko?!
Even though I told you I'll buy them in the store.
Well, just accept them, don't be so modest.
You know that you're like a father to Nami and I.
If you say so.
What're you doing?
Well...
I'm trying to use the Den Den Mushi to call the Marine headquarters to complain
But I'm not getting a single response!
Complain?
That's right!
Do they really think they can distribute this improper poster to the entire world?!
Instead of bounty hunters, lovestruck suitors will gather to go after her! Unacceptable!
But you liked that picture, right?
Since you enlarged it.
Well, it's fine, besides...
They're keeping the promise they made to you...
If by any chance you take away Nami's smile,
I'll personally go and kill you!
That's the evidence.
Well, that's true but...
That's the pirates problem!
Then, would you prefer an ugly photo?
No! That's unacceptable!
The Grand Line
Sakura Kingdom Chopper's Hometown
Doctor Kureha.
Dolton, why did you call me?
I'm a very busy person!
I'm very sorry.
I just had to show you this.
What do you want? The secret to my youth?
Anyway Dolton, why don't you go live in the castle as king?
I can lend you a room.
No, thank you, I'm already used to living in this village.
Besides, I like eating chestnuts.
It's the Straw Hat kid and the others...
Wanted posters came out after the recent incident.
Chopper.
I think they made a mistake about the amount.
It's fine since I got to see his face.
That's right...
This is the best news I've gotten in a while.
The Grand Line
White soil Island Baltigo.
The rebel army has succeded at the South Blue St. Urea!
One more kingdom has fallen...
They did it!
With this, the other day news about North Blue...
Don't be glad about a victory!
This is war.
I-I'm sorry...
And this is?
It's Straw Hat Luffy.
The one who took down Crocodile at Arabasta.
After the events at Enies Lobby, the government couldn't keep hiding his big group of pirates.
The crew's total bounty is 667 million and 50 belly.
Their Captain is the marine Garp's...
Where are you going?
To get some fresh air.
Live according to your thoughts, Luffy.
There are times when the era suddenly determines everything...
The World's Most Wanted Man
The Revolutionary Dragon
Monkey D. Dragon
Question the world!
The day we meet will come.
Oh! Ace!
We go back three days before the bounties of the Strawhat crew surprised the whole world.
An event occurred on a certain island...
This is the Grand Line, Banaro Island.
Commander.
Knock it off! Commander is a word only those respectful of that person are allowed to say.
Stop mocking.
So you're the famous Fire Fist Ace...
Yeah, that's right.
Nice to meet you.
It seems now you've become quite a Captain, right?
Captain of the Blackbeard pirates, Marshall D. Teach.
What's wrong, Ace?!
It's been a long time!
How did you know I was here?
Teach, stop asking useless questions.
You took a man's life.
You must have a comprehension of the current situation.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, I know.
Then, let me say just one thing.
Ace, will you join my crew?!
Rule the world with me!
I've already planned every single thing.
Whitebeard's time is over already.
It is I who'll become the Pirate King!
First, I'll go to Water Seven from here to kill Straw Hat Luffy and hand him over to the government.
Luffy...?!
What did you say...?
Oh, You know him?
I won't let you lay a finger on him.
He's my little brother!
And, of course I'm not gonna join....
...your crew.
Seems like we have a guy without manners here.
Fire Gun!
Flame Commandment...
Fire Pillar!
Auger, Burgess.
You stay out of this!
You're still no match for that man!
Step back!
Sorry.
Fire Fist!
Captain!
Captain.
Lay it off, you guys!
Stay back!
I understand, Ace.
You want to kill me, right?
That's right, the murder of a crewmate is a big crime.
It's true I killed the 4th Division Commander Thatch!
I had no choice!
He had the devil fruit I wanted.
The ship's rule was that the guy who finds it gets to eat it.
I memorized all devil fruit shapes from a book, so...
I immediately knew that was the one I was looking for.
I stayed all those decades on Whitebeard’s ship thinking it would raise the chance to run into that fruit.
If I had run out of luck, I'd have given up on it, but...
That fruit came into my friend's possession!
And after killing Thatch... you stole it.
Well, it was just the spur of the moment.
This ability has chosen me, Ace!
With this, I have become the strongest man, Ace!
Look!
It's unique even among logia!
Ace, your body is fire, right?
I am...
Darkness!
Look! It's that black smoke from before!
Those pirates are still in town!
They're still up to something!
At this rate, the town will be destroyed!
Don't get near them!
Just run!
Darkness?
That's right, Commander Ace.
I can't get killed by you!
Out of all the devil fruits recorded in history, the one with this power is known as the most evil of them all!
A logia, the Darkness Fruit.
I've become a man of darkness!
I'll give you a taste of its power right now!
Do as you like.
What're you doing?! Hurry up!
The Captain is rampaging!
Hurry up and take cover!
Even we might get involved!
Stand up!
Something is crawling on the ground.
It's that thing that comes out of his body.
So scary!
It's like a black hole on the ground!
Looks like we could get sucked in!
Hurry up and escape!
Find shelter!
Take refuge in the forest!
Run to the coast!
Darkness is gravity.
The power to drag in everything...
and to keep all light from escaping,
infinite gravity.
Even so, it doesn't seem to be reaching me.
I'm not going after you yet...
Just stand there and take a look at the town.
Black Hole!
The town is... being swallowed into the ground!
Why?!
W-What's going on?!
The gravity of darkness condenses every object with its infinite power.
Crushing them!
Am I dreaming?
Our town has...
Has it vanished?
Right now I'll show you...
What became of it!
Liberation!
The town has...
Turned into just a pile of wood.
You get it now, Ace?!
This is the power I've gained!
Firefly...
Fiery Doll!
Hot!
I understand pretty well the greatness of the power of darkness.
But, this is quite strange...
If you're a logia, you should be able to dodge an attack such as this.
I already told you...
Darkness drags in everything.
Bullets, blades, strikes, fire and even lightning.
I can't dodge attacks like the rest of you do.
My body absorbs much more pain than a normal human.
But, in exchange for that risk there's one more thing I'm capable of absorbing!
Dark Vortex!
The gravity of darkness can accurately absorb the "entity" of a devil fruit user!
Gravity?!
And thus, my body can...!
How is it?
Have you figured it out yet, Ace?
No way...!
It's been a while since someone actually hit you, right?
Ace.
You understood the moment I grabbed you.
The other thing my darkness can absorb is...
Devil fruit powers!
In other words, by being touched, those with devil fruit abilities are unable to use their ability!
Logia, Zoan, Paramecia....
All those overconfident devil fruit users in the world...
I've obtained the ability to expose their weakness!
So it's fine if I don't get caught.
I just proved to you that you can't get away from the gravity of darkness!
Dark Vortex!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Ace...!
Damn!
A flame lance?!
He almost broke my neck!
Quite a troublesome ability he has.
Cross Fire!
Another banana rock is being destroyed...
What's going on?
This isn't humane.
Not only this town...
The whole island will get...!
I always thought that devil fruit users relied too much on their abilities,
and if they happened to lose them, they would become rather fragile, but...
As expected of a Commander on Whitebeard's ship...
His basic combat abilities are also quite fearsome.
Well then, today once again...
Fate has separated our ways.
Everything is useless before darkness.
Even that strength of yours.
However, it would be a shame to waste that power.
Ace! Join my crew!
If I surrender my power to you, then there was no point in me being a man.
I definitely won't live with regrets.
Got that, idiot?
How long can you keep living like that in this world...
It's a shame, Ace.
Die by the darkness!
Great Flame Commandment...!!
Flame Emperor!!!
The sun or the darkness.
There can only be one winner!
I'll make Whitebeard...
The King.
The Grand Line Banaro Island duel...
The fight between those two pirates,
Will be remembered as the trigger for a big event that has yet to come.
Translation, Cornman @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Initial timing, Hedi @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Quality checking, Sewil
Editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, MaideV and Halee
Raw providing, SOFCJ-Raws